http://www.deslock.com/privacy.php

DESLOCK is now ESET ENDPOINT ENCRYPTION
HOMESUPPORTLOGIN
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of deslock.com web sites
- the Site(s)
This Privacy Policy applies to these Site(s) and not necessarily to other ESET sites. When leaving any Site(s), please read the privacy policy applicable
to the site you are thereafter visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site(s).
Entering and using the Site(s) you declare your agreement with this privacy statement.
By using these Site(s), you expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that your Personal Information gained with registration
on these Site(s), or in connection with your use of the Site(s), with respect to the Site(s), may be transferred across international borders
to server locations supporting the Site(s) (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration)
for operating and developing the Site(s), including transfers to DESlock ltd. subcontractors, agents or representatives, who perform tasks
related to the Site(s) and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant databases.
Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected
DESlock ltd. (hereinafter "DESlock") is committed to the protection of privacy of the Site(s) visitors.
Please note that DESlock may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to
trusted third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.
Personal Information
DESlock collects Personal Information for the purposes of provision, development and personalization of the Site(s) and any other DESlock sites,
services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics and customer care. Specifically, DESlock collects personal information for the purposes of
personal communication with you in order to respond to your questions, and fulfill your requests. Such information may include, among other information, your name,
address, e-mail address and telephone number. These data will be used in the events you have so consented, to contact you for direct marketing purposes via mail,
e-mail or phone to conduct market research, and to inform you of and get your feedback on upcoming products, services and/or promotions. If you send us product
orders, service requirements or if you send any material to the Site(s), we might have to contact you in order to gain additional information necessary
for processing or fulfillment of your orders and/or requirements. Your Personal Information will not be revealed to any third parties without your prior
consent, unless required otherwise by legal regulations, or cases, when it is necessary for proceeding of your order, fulfilling of your request, or
providing interactive customer service and DESlock's products and services improvement. At the same time you are granting DESlock the right to provide the
information you submitted to DESlock for above purposes to the partners cooperating with DESlock.
Personal Information Security
Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or
any other media or terminal, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker-proof", DESlock has endeavored to take appropriate
measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your Personal Information. For example when
collecting or transferring sensitive data, e.g. cash card information, we use encrypting technology.
Accuracy of Collected Data
DESlock will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any in-complete, inaccurate or outdated personal information
retained by DESlock in connection with the operation of the Site(s).
Visitors Identification
Generally, you may use these Site(s) for information purposes without giving personal information and informing DESlock who you are. But, from time to time,
DESlock or its third-party designees may place information on your computer to allow DESlock to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as "cookies".
The cookies are commonly used on many websites. Cookies are stored on your hard disc in the computer, not on the Site(s). DESlock or its third-party designees will use only
information, they themselves placed in cookies through the Site(s) or other DESlock's web sites.
Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. By means of cookies DESlock is able to further
develop and improve the Site(s).
As to the former, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type your log-in name each time and without having to add products to your
shopping list each time in between two visits, if the transaction was not finished in previous visit.
No personal information about you is gathered through the use of these types of cookies. In other words, cookies are identifying your computer, not you.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, or you want to be notified when a cookie is set, you can configure your browser, if the browser allows given settings.
If you choose to decline cookies, please, be aware, that you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site(s), nor you will be able
to download certain contents and/or to take part in certain transactions on the Site(s).
Besides, the Site(s) may use different technology, which enables to DESlock to collect certain technical information, for example: your IP address, type of operational
system in your computer, internet browser type and addresses of connected sites, in order to improve provided services.
DESlock may use third party scripts on our sites to optimize the effectiveness of DESlock's ads appearing on other parties' sites, such as the
type and/or frequency of ads, promotions, or other marketing messages the customer views.
The information collected is not personally identifiable and is limited to the minimum information necessary to optimize effectiveness.
Available Cookie Opt-out - Google Analytics: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
To opt out from behavioral advertising by networks adhering to the Network Advertising Initiative visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Minors
No information may be submitted to DESlock via the Site(s) by persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor
or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to DESlock via
the Site(s), with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country.
Modification of the Privacy Policy
DESlock reserves the right to change or modify at any time this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or deny access to the Site(s), or their content without prior notice.
Service Specific Terms
DESlock may have separate terms for different services (for example the Terms of Usage), in which the service specific terms and conditions might be set
forth (including data protection).
Legal
Privacy
© 1992–2019 ESET, spol. s r.o. All rights reserved. Trademarks used herein are trademarks or registered trademarks of ESET, spol. s r.o. or ESET North America. All other names and brands are registered trademarks of their respective companies.
We use cookies on our website to enhance your browsing experience.
Read more
